If you are truly honorable and keep your promises,
then give me my sister's medicine.
Give me the medicine, and I'll die without complaint.
Don't you want to kill me?
Come on.
I understand now.
You are provoking me into giving you the medicine.
Daoist, we had a deal.
You'd give me the medicine once we left Wuyou City.
My sister's illness really can't be delayed any longer.
You know...
I promised you.
Help us complete the mission,
and I will naturally hand over the medicine.
I knew you were going to complete the Master of Wuyou Cave's mission,
so I waited here for you.
I heard some news
related to Wuyou City.
Want to hear it?
What news?
Give me the medicine.
You speak first.
You give it first.
Speak.
Someone is going to assassinate the Emperor,
but it's not you.
Aunt Yi'an,
something happened to Han.
Tonight, my sister was supposed to see me off on a boat.
On the way,
we suddenly encountered an inspection by the Imperial City Department.
I got off the carriage
and went to the pier. When I looked for my sister again,
the driver said
a group of thugs suddenly rushed out
and kidnapped my sister and Zhu'er.
What?
I heard that at the pier,
women are often kidnapped and smuggled out of Dongjing by boat.
The boat hasn't left yet.
Those thugs
couldn't have gone far.
My current identity is awkward.
I ask Aunt Yi'an
to immediately ask the guards to rescue my sister.
At this hour,
where can I find guards?
Lord Zhou.
Go find Lord Zhou.
I just wrote
this letter in the carriage.
Please give it to him, Aunt.
He will definitely be able to save my sister.
I don't know what you and Han are doing,
but disregarding your own safety
is definitely a big mistake.
When she comes back,
I will punish her severely.
Men,
prepare the carriage.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Go.
Stop crying.
Check the whole cellar immediately.
Check all these women
as well.
Yes.
Nothing unusual in the cellar.
The number of women and smuggled salt match.
There's nothing unusual either.
Holy Master,
we just received this secret report.
Those Liangshan rebels
are probably not going to attack the merchant ships, but the cellar.
Time is too tight.
To transfer all this smuggled salt
and these women,
I'm afraid
it's impossible.
If they really have the ability to expose this smuggled salt
and the women trafficking,
then put on a show,
and frame
that corrupt official Zhu Mian from the imperial court as the mastermind.
Please instruct me, Holy Master,
what should
I do?
Do you recognize these two people?
Lord Zhu Mian's favorite concubine.
The owner of Yunxiang Pavilion.
These two had an affair
and tried to escape Zhu Mian's control.
Let's use them as a warning to others.
Spare my life!
Shopkeeper Lou,
spare me!
You are wise, Holy Master.
Spare me, Shopkeeper Lou.
Shopkeeper Lou, please spare us.
Shopkeeper Lou.
Please have mercy.
Now you know to be afraid?
What were you doing before?
Shopkeeper Lou.
At this hour,
Yunxiang Pavilion is full of guests.
If we bring the abducted women to the main hall
and draw a crowd,
this scheme will be exposed.
Then our mission will be accomplished.
That's simple.
Chen Wu, you guard the door.
Brother Li Lang,
gather the guests.
That way, we can get this done.
Before tonight,
one of these two wretches
was Lord Zhu Mian's favorite concubine.
The other
is the popular owner of Yunxiang Pavilion.
Just because they conspired to escape from Dongjing City,
they ended up like this.
Neither the favorite concubine nor the owner could escape.
All of you,
no matter your status,
their fate
will be your fate.
Come in, please.
Thank you.
Please take a seat.
I'll get you some tea.
Enjoy, sir.
My lady.
Don't be afraid, sisters.
She's already dead.
That woman
who just beat someone to death in front of us
wants us to believe
that the one who abducted us tonight
is that scumbag official Zhu Mian.
Zhu Mian is indeed detestable,
and might even have participated in this illegal trade.
But the one actually doing the illegal trade tonight
is someone else.
This is the cellar of Yunxiang Pavilion.
There must be ambushes everywhere outside.
Once we get out,
run towards the banquet hall.
There are many people there.
Just shout loudly,
"Murder!"
Someone will definitely come to save us.
Understood?
Really?
I'm scared.
Is that clear?
Clear.
Go.
Murder!
Help!
Murder in the cellar!
Murder! Help!
Murder!
Go check it out, there's a commotion at Yunxiang Pavilion!
Hurry.
Help! Murder!
Save me!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Murder! Help!
Hurry.
Help! Murder here!
Murder! Help!
Something happened in Yunxiang Pavilion.
Right here, hurry.
My lord.
It's confirmed that the villains are in the pavilion.
Please block all exits immediately.
Sanniangzi.
If Li Yi'an hadn't come forward to testify,
I would be deploying troops without authorization.
If we really catch the assassins and make a merit, that's fine.
If we cause trouble and make a mistake,
I will definitely hold you responsible.
Don't worry, my lord.
You will definitely make a merit this time.
At the very least, you saved the female members of the Zhao family.
If you catch the villains,
it will be an even greater merit.
Alright.
I'll trust you this once.